<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>List of posts on sahli.net</title><link>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in List of posts on sahli.net</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 11:52:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techie.sahli.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Elm?</title><link>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/09/29/what-is-elm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 11:52:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/09/29/what-is-elm/</guid><description>A delightful language for reliable webapps. Elm is a domain-specific programming language for creating web browser-based graphical user interfaces.
It's main features are:
Immutability Static types Module system Interoperability with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript It's main advantages are:
No runtime exceptions Great performance Small assets The main advantage for a developer is that when the Elm compiler is happy with the code, browsers and users will be happy too (the same feeling Go developers have).</description></item><item><title>What is Hugo?</title><link>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/03/what-is-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 11:52:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/03/what-is-hugo/</guid><description>A framework for building websites The world’s fastest framework for building websites. https://gohugo.io/
It is very easy to preview your website. Run
hugo server and then open http://localhost:1313 in your favourite webbrowser.
And to build your website.
hugo Publish the generated website in the public directory to a webserver. Done.
For a deeper start have a look at the Quick Start guide.
Resources gohugo.io Quick Start / Hugo Docs Hugo Project on Github Publish your site with Github Actions and Pages</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Go</title><link>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/02/welcome-to-go/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 20:09:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techie.sahli.net/blog/2020/02/welcome-to-go/</guid><description>Golang as common language In January 2020 I took the chance to present my talk &amp;ldquo;Welcome to Go&amp;rdquo; about the Go Programming Language at Guild42.ch. Guild42.ch is an association that organizes events on topics related to software development in Berne, Switzerland.
Over 85 developers from around Berne were interested in the topic. Until there I was telling only Swiss Post stuff about Golang and argued about why the language is very useful.</description></item></channel></rss>